(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T01:56:14.437505",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
supported by Pocky & ACL
Ayunda Risu
Kureiji Ollie
Vestia Zeta
Moona Hoshinova
Anya Melfissa
Kaela Kovalskia
Airani Iofifteen
Pavolia Reine
Kobo Kanaeru
Ayunda Risu: TERIMA KASIH!
Ayunda Risu: Thank you!
Kureiji Ollie: Berkat kalian, kami bisa bersinar! Beribu-ribu terima kasih
Kureiji Ollie: Thanks to you, we can shine! Thousands of thanks
Vestia Zeta: Terima kasih udah bikin stage ini & hidup kami lebih berwarna!
Vestia Zeta: Thank you for making this stage & our lives more colorful!
Moona Hoshinova: Terima Kasih!!
Moona Hoshinova: Thank you!!
Anya Melfissa: TERIMA KASIH BANYAK!!!!
Anya Melfissa: Thank you so much!!!!
Kaela Kovalskia: Terima Kasih!! Kalian Semua Keren BGT!
Kaela Kovalskia: Thank you!! You guys are so awesome!
Airani Iofifteen: Terima Kasih!!!
Airani Iofifteen: Thank you!!!
Pavolia Reine: Makasih ya! :)
Pavolia Reine: Thank you! :)
Kobo Kanaeru: terima kasih
Kobo Kanaeru: thank you
Ayo mulai!!
Let's begin!!
CHROMATIC FUTURE hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
身も心も…
Body and soul...
この手で make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine
Wow wow wow
Wow wow wow (Yeah)
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと…
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever...
君を視るたび 上書きされてく欲望に
Every time I look at you, my desire is overwritten
重なる eyes, eyes, eyes
Our overlapping eyes, eyes, eyes
胸打つ your smile, smile, smile
Your smile, smile, smile strikes my heart
ねぇ その姿 形 総てが拍車掛けてく
Hey, your figure, your shape, everything spurs me on
恋から愛、愛、愛
From crush to love, love, love
毎秒おかしくなってく
I'm going crazy by the second
手を伸ばせば もう届く距離
If I reach out, we are close enough to touch
危険な “a to z” 試したい
I want to try a dangerous 'A to Z'
穏やかに 恋したい
I want to love you peacefully
どんなシーンも 私に見せて
Show me every side of you
このまま stay by my side
Stay by my side just like this
“どこにも行かないで”
“Don't go anywhere”
Aww! 100% 純粋な愛だから
Aww! Because it's 100% pure love,
ねぇ、いいでしょ？
hey, is that okay?
止められない感情 その腕で抱き締めてよ
Hold this unstoppable feeling tight in your arms
(boy, i wanna touch your love)
Aww! 遠くからじゃ嫌
Aww! I don't want to be far away
ずっともっと 近くで認め合いたい
I want us to acknowledge each other much closer forever
暴れ狂う衝動 持て余すだけならツライ
It hurts if I can't handle this wild impulse
Hey me! What's wrong with me?
(Say)
何も問題ない 普通だし
There's nothing wrong, I'm normal
(My name)
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you right now
最初は “声を聴く” それだけでよかった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough
だけど次第に why? 我が儘になった
But gradually, why did I become so selfish?
誰かに笑いかける その仕草に
When you smile at someone else,
苛立ち隠せない自分に気づいた
I realized I couldn't hide my irritation
「独り占めにしたい」
“I want to keep you all to myself”
いっそ、鎖に繋いで
I'd rather chain you up
止められない感情
These unstoppable feelings,
その手で抱きしめてよ
hold them tight in your hands.
遠くからだよ ずっともっと近くで
Not from afar, but much, much closer,
認め合いたい
I want us to accept each other.
暴れだす衝動 乗って
Riding on this wild impulse,
甘そうだけどラスト
it seems sweet, but it's the end.
Tell me what's wrong with me
何もないない 太刀打ちできないみたい
There's nothing left, seems I can't compete at all.
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you,
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you right now.
Wow...
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever.
Wow...
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever.
逃げるなら今だよ 勝機を願っちゃって
If you're going to run, now is the time, pray for a chance to win!
ハメ食らって!
Falling into a trap!
ピンチだ、脱出、脱出、脱出!
It's a pinch, escape, escape, escape!
Are you ready? Mau sembunyi di mana? Menit, naik, lari, ya 15 minutes
Are you ready? Where do you want to hide? Minutes, climbing, running, yes 15 minutes.
Memejamkan mata, menghitung satu sampai sepuluh, kini, hora, daraka...
Closing my eyes, counting from one to ten, now, look, someone...
I just escape game!
Standby nya, mau jujur, aku...
Standby, to be honest, I...
Round one, round two, round three...
Satu, dua, tiga, empat, lima, enam, tujuh, delapan, sembilan, sepuluh, sebelas, dua belas, tiga belas, empat belas, lima belas, enam belas, tujuh belas, delapan belas, sembilan belas, dua puluh!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Aku tidak peduli keberuntungan kayak ginian, percaya sama diriku sendiri
I don't care about this kind of luck, I believe in myself!
Day by day, shoudou... Ara ara...
Day by day, impulse... Oh my...
決めたこと全部 ピンをさした
I've pinned down everything I decided.
笑ってくれたっていい
It's fine if you laugh at me.
冷められない
I can't cool down.
Victory to the world then...
願うはきっと叶うよ
My wish will surely come true.
見てて、見てて、見ててよ、この強気 いらっしゃって
Watch me, watch me, watch this confidence of mine, and come on in!
Satu, dua, tiga, empat, lima, enam, tujuh, delapan, sembilan, sepuluh, sebelas, dua belas, tiga belas, empat belas, lima belas, enam belas, tujuh belas, delapan belas, sembilan belas, dua puluh!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Aku tidak peduli keberuntungan kayak ginian, percaya sama diriku sendiri
I don't care about this kind of luck, I believe in myself!
Day by day, shoudou... Ara ara...
Day by day, impulse... Oh my...
決めたこと全部 ピンをさした
I've pinned down everything I decided.
笑ってくれたっていい
It's fine if you laugh at me.
冷められない
I can't cool down.
Siji, loro, telu, papat, limo, enem, pitu, wolu, songo, sepuluh...
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
Aku tidak peduli keberuntungan kayak ginian, percaya sama diriku sendiri
I don't care about this kind of luck, I believe in myself!
Are you ready? Mau sembunyi di mana? Menit, naik, lari, ya 15 minutes
Are you ready? Where do you want to hide? Minutes, climbing, running, yes 15 minutes.
Memejamkan mata, menghitung satu sampai sepuluh, kini, hora, daraka...
Closing my eyes, counting from one to ten, now, look, someone...
Victory to the world then...
Tolong sama-sama...
Please, together...
Asyik...
It's fun...
Kole... kowe...
Here... you...
Siji, loro, telu... papat, limo...
One, two, three, four, five...
Ayo, anya, ngeramekke!
Come on, Anya, make it lively!
Ayo, Reine... Ayo, Ollie...
Come on, Reine... Come on, Ollie...
Ayo, Risu, mana suaranya?!
Come on, Risu, where's your voice?!
Hei! Hei! Hei! Hei!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Day by day... Shoudou... Ara ara...
Day by day, impulse... Oh my...
決めたこと全部 ピンをさした
I've pinned down everything I decided.
笑ってくれたっていい
It's fine if you laugh at me.
冷められない
I can't cool down.
Day by day, もっと... ara ara
Day by day, more... oh my
私たちのシグナル カウントとって
Take our signal count!
笑ってくれたっていい
It's fine if you laugh at me.
冷められない
I can't cool down.
Victory to the world then...
絶対追い抜くよ あの光で軌道を
I will absolutely overtake you, with that light's orbit,
忘れられないほどの
unforgettable enough...
勝利を願っちゃって
Praying for victory!
強気で行こう、GG!
Let's go strong, GG!
ふぅー...
Fuuuh...
Siapa di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan?
Who here is tired of life?
Aku! Aku!
Me! Me!
Kalau capek, enaknya gimana nih, Kaela?
If you're tired, what's the best thing to do, Kaela?
Napas saja!
Just breathe!
Cakep!
Cool!
Bukankah sudah biasa
Isn't it usual
Di titik lelah kecewa
At the point of exhaustion and disappointment
saat dunia tak berjalan
When the world doesn't go
semestinya, oh-oh
the way it's supposed to, oh-oh.
mungkin sudahlah saatnya
Maybe now is the time
kau coba lepaskan saja
for you to just let it go.
tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why ever again.
jika memang
If indeed...
jawaban tak kau dapatkan
...you can't get the answer,
jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
don't cry, just try to get through its riddles.
relakanlah
Just accept it,
karena pada akhirnya
because in the end,
kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
you are stronger than you think.
dahlah saja
Just let it be.
oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be.
jalani saja
Just move on.
dahlah saja
Just let it be.
oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be.
jalani saja
Just move on.
mau gimana lagi?
What else can you do?
walau kadang mati rasa
Even if you sometimes feel numb,
bahkan hingga tak berdaya
or even completely helpless,
dan usahamu terasa sia-sia
and your efforts feel completely in vain.
jika memang
If indeed...
jawaban tak kau dapatkan
...you can't get the answer,
jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
don't cry, just try to get through its riddles.
relakanlah
Just accept it,
karena pada akhirnya
because in the end,
kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
you are stronger than you think.
lepas semua kendali
Let go of all control,
tancap gas dan berlari
step on the gas and run,
terima dan sudahi
accept it and put an end to it.
jika memang
If indeed...
jawaban tak kau dapatkan
...you can't get the answer,
jangan tangisi
don't cry over it,
coba lalui
try to get through...
teka-tekinya
...its riddles.
relakanlah
Just accept it,
karena pada akhirnya
because in the end,
kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
you are stronger than you think.
You are stronger than you think.
dahlah saja
Just let it be.
oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be.
jalani saja
Just move on.
dahlah saja
Just let it be.
oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be.
jalani saja
Just move on.
maikka
Oh well.
Halo Comic Frontier!
Hello Comic Frontier!
Halo!
Hello!
Welcome to...
hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary Live...
Chromatic Future!
Yeah!
Wah, gila gila gila!
Wow, this is crazy, crazy, crazy!
Makasih banyak semuanya udah pada datang ke konser 5 tahun kita ya!
Thank you so much, everyone, for coming to our 5th-anniversary concert!
Wah, nggak berasa nggak sih udah 5 tahun aja?
Wow, don't you feel like it's already been 5 years?
Kalau gitu, kita mulai dari perkenalan diri dulu nggak sih? Mulai dari aku, aku, aku!
In that case, should we start with self-introductions? Starting with me, me, me!
Oke, oke, oke... Di belakang aja.
Okay, okay, okay... Let me do it at the back.
A-A-Avisans! Tato! Tato!
Aku secret agent dari hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
I'm the secret agent from hololive Indonesia Gen 3. Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you too! Iya, iya, iya! Oke, next Kaela!
Nice to meet you too! Yes, yes, yes! Okay, next, Kaela!
Oke, oke, oke. Kaela, grinding every time, the blacksmith from hololive ID Gen 3.
Okay, okay, okay. Kaela, grinding every time, the blacksmith from hololive ID Gen 3.
I'm Kaela Kovalskia, nice to meet you all!
Yeah! Kaela! Kaela!
Next, next, next! Kobo, Kobo, Kobo!
Heii! Kobo Kanaeru, rain shaman at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Hey! Kobo Kanaeru, rain shaman at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Kobokerz! Mana suaranya?!
Kobokerz! Let me hear your voice!
Wooo!
Nah, bertiga kami dari...
So, the three of us are from...
hololive Indonesia Gen 3!
Halo semuanya!
Hello, everyone!
Wah, nggak nyangka juga deh konser 5th Anniversary hololive ID ini akhirnya ada juga.
Wow, I didn't expect that this hololive ID 5th Anniversary concert would finally happen.
Dari lagu pertama aja udah keren banget, guys. Kerasa nggak sih?
Even from the very first song, it was already so cool, guys. Did you feel it?
Masih semangat, nggak? Iya, masih, masih!
Are you still energetic? Yes, still, still!
Keliatan parasnya ada adrenaline rush, kan ya?
It's obvious from your faces that there's an adrenaline rush, right?
Hah, pengen lari aku rasanya nih.
Ah, I feel like running.
Woi, woi, woi, eeee... mau kemana?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, where are you going?
Mau kemana? Mau kemana?
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Nanti keringetan, lho. Nanti keringetan.
You'll get sweaty later. You'll get sweaty.
Ah... Kalau Kaela gimana?
Ah... How about you, Kaela?
Aduh, seru banget! Aku nggak nyangka sih, sampai aku bisa ada di sini ya.
Oh, it's so exciting! I didn't expect that I could be here.
Tapi ini ngomong-ngomong konser-nya masih panjang banget. Jadi kalian tetap semangat ya sampai akhir!
But by the way, this concert is still very long, so keep your spirits up until the end!
Sampai akhir! Semangat, semangat, semangat, semangat, semangat!
Until the end! Keep it up, keep it up, keep it up!
Eh, tapi ngomongin konser dari tadi, emang pada tahu judul konser-nya apa?
By the way, talking about the concert, does everyone actually know the title of this concert?
Judul konser kita kali ini adalah Chromatic Future!
The title of our concert this time is Chromatic Future!
Ada yang tahu nggak artinya apa? Ayo, absen!
Does anyone know what it means? Come on, roll call!
Nah, ini, Kobo paling tahu!
Now, this, Kobo knows it best!
Nih, ya...
Here...
Yang... Yang ngejelasin yang paling tinggi! Yuk, let's go!
The one... The tallest one should explain! Come on, let's go!
Bisa gitu ya? Ya udahlah, ya udah, ya udah.
Is that how it is? Oh well, okay then.
Nih ya, guys, ya. Buat kalian yang belum tahu, Chromatic Future itu artinya tuh masa depan yang berwarna-warni.
Here, guys. For those of you who don't know, Chromatic Future means a colorful future.
Jadi karena Hololive Indonesia kan udah 5 tahun nih.
So since Hololive Indonesia has been around for 5 years now,
Kita sama-sama dari hari satu sampai sekarang.
we've been together from day one until now.
Nah, jadi itu untuk ke depannya, kita tuh juga harapannya tuh kita bisa nyiptain waktu dan memori yang berwarna-warni...
So for the future, our hope is also that we can create colorful times and memories...
...sama seluruh fans dari Hololive Indonesia!
...together with all Hololive Indonesia fans!
Ya, gitu! Betul, Kaela. Bagus banget! Catet, catet!
Yes, that's right! Correct, Kaela. Great job! Take notes, take notes!
Oh iya, iya, iya, iya!
Oh yes, yes, yes, yes!
Nah, kalian sekarang udah pada tahu kan? Karena tadi udah dijelasin sama Kaela.
Now you all know, right? Since Kaela already explained it.
Kalau gitu, konser-nya kan udah mulai nih.
In that case, since the concert has started,
Kalian mau nge-post soal konser ini di medsos,
if you want to post about this concert on social media,
jangan lupa hashtag #HoloIDChromaticFuture ya!
don't forget to use the hashtag #HoloIDChromaticFuture!
Karena kita pengen banget lihat kalian tuh... apa sih? Pengen lihat semangat kalian!
Because we really want to see your... what is it? We want to see your enthusiasm!
Ya, itu! Betul banget, ya nggak?
Yes, that! Absolutely correct, right?
Jangan typo, jangan typo!
Don't make typos, don't make typos!
Asyik! Share ke semua, oke?
Awesome! Share it with everyone, okay?
Jadi, tapi... jujur deh, kalian tuh pas dibilang,
So, but... honestly, when you were told,
kita bakal konser lho di Indonesia, kalian pada kaget nggak sih?
we're having a concert in Indonesia, were you surprised?
Halo, di-dengerin?
Hello, are you listening?
Betul! Aku setuju juga.
That's right! I agree too.
Aku merasakan empati terhadap, ini, adik saya Zeta. "Iya, iya, empati, iya, iya."
I feel empathy towards my younger sister Zeta. "Yes, empathy, yes."
Kalau Kaela gimana, Kaela?
How about you, Kaela?
Aku juga waktu itu nggak nyangka banget kayak, "Hah? Beneran? Ini real kah?" gitu kan.
I also couldn't believe it at the time, like, "Huh? Really? Is this real?" like that.
Kayak, "Loh, bisa gitu? Akhirnya!" Mana udah bersembilan di Indonesia pula, ya kan?
Like, "Wow, is that possible? Finally!" And all nine of us are in Indonesia too, right?
Keren banget! Keren banget! Keren banget, iya.
It's so cool! So cool! So cool, yes.
Ini kan konser pertama Hololive Indonesia yang bersembilan.
This is Hololive Indonesia's first concert with all nine members.
Sebenarnya tuh, nggak hanya ini tuh momen terbesar dan terpenting juga...
Actually, not only is this the biggest and most important moment...
...untuk fans Hololive Indonesia, tapi...
...for Hololive Indonesia fans, but...
...seluruh dunia juga pasti bakal nonton nggak sih? Ya, nggak?
...the whole world will definitely be watching, right?
Jawab!
Answer!
Iya, iya. Makasih, makasih semuanya. Tapi... "Makasih!"
Yes, yes. Thank you, thank you everyone. But... "Thank you!"
...tentu saja ini pencapaiannya nggak bakal cuma sampai di sini aja, kan?
...of course this achievement won't stop just here, right?
Jadi next-nya mungkin kita bisa apa ya, dominating the world gitu. We ready! Ready, ready, ready!
So next, maybe we can dominate the world. We're ready! Ready, ready, ready!
Ready, ready, ready! Betul banget Kaela, Zeta!
Ready, ready, ready! That's so true Kaela, Zeta!
Selain dari dukungan fans, in this opportunity,
In addition to the fans' support, on this opportunity,
kita juga mau mengucapkan terima kasih untuk semua sponsor yang mendukung terjadinya konser ini. Terima kasih!
we also want to thank all the sponsors who supported this concert. Thank you!
Makasih! Makasih, makasih, makasih semuanya! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you! Thank you, thank you, thank you everyone! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Eh, tapi ngomong-ngomong, di konser ini kayaknya ada yang beda, nggak sih?
Oh, but by the way, does something feel different about this concert?
Kaela, kamu nyadar nggak? Soalnya kamu paling peka, kan?
Kaela, did you notice? Because you are the most sensitive, right?
Sadar lah. Kalau Kobo mah nggak bakalan sadar.
Of course I did. Kobo would never notice.
Nih, nih, nih, yang beda tuh kali ini tuh model kita. Ini model baru nih!
Look, look, look, what's different this time is our models. These are new models!
Gemes, kan? Lucu, lucu!
Cute, right? So cute, so cute!
Iya, betul, betul! Lucu, lucu, lucu!
Yes, that's right! Cute, cute, cute!
Kamera, kameranya deketin ke aku!
Camera, zoom the camera in on me!
Kameranya deketin ke aku! Nih, nih, nih. Kalian mau lihat keimutan Kobo? Nih, nih.
Zoom the camera in on me! Look here. Do you want to see Kobo's cuteness? Look.
Pose ini. Eh... oh...
This pose. Oh...
Wait, wait, wait. Sini, sini, sini. Ini kamera diambil Kobo semua, nggak sih?
Wait, wait, wait. Come here. The camera is being monopolized by Kobo, isn't it?
Sini, sini. Ke aku juga, ke aku juga. Jangan Kobo doang. Sini, sini, kamera, kamera! "Sini, sini!"
Come here. Show me too, show me too. Not just Kobo. Come here, camera! "Come here!"
Kamera, kamera, kamera! Sini, Kobo lagi!
Camera, camera, camera! Come here, Kobo again!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Mulai, mulai, mulai...
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. It's starting, starting...
...semua kamera diambil.
...all cameras are taken.
Oke, oke, oke. Kalau gitu...
Okay, okay, okay. In that case...
Aduh, aduh, aduh. Sampai kehabisan napas.
Oh dear, I'm out of breath.
Jangan rebutan di depan konser!
Don't fight in front of the concert!
Iya. "Iya, iya, iya, iya."
Yes. "Yes, yes, yes, yes."
Tapi, kalau Zeta udah...
But, since Zeta already...
Takut, ih. Iya, ya udah deh.
I'm scared. Okay, fine.
Kalau gak boleh rebutan komputer sama Zeta, hmmm...
If we can't fight over the computer with Zeta, hmmm...
sebel banget!
...how annoying!
Kita main aja deh sama penonton.
Let's just play with the audience instead.
Kobo pengen deh coba kita teriakin penonton,
Kobo wants us to try screaming at the audience,
karena kan tadi mereka sudah teriakin kita.
because they screamed at us earlier.
Iya, iya, iya. Maksudnya kita teriak...
Yes, yes, yes. I mean we scream...
Maksudnya kita teriakin bareng penonton...
I mean, we scream together with the audience...
Penonton-tachi!
Dear audience!
Betul! Teriaknya bareng penonton,
Right! Scream together with the audience,
jangan teriakin penontonnya ya.
not screaming at the audience.
Iya, gitu maksudnya!
Yes, that's what I meant!
Soalnya kan habis ini kita harus nyanyi,
Because we have to sing after this,
jadi kita harus simpan suara dulu, gak sih?
so we should save our voices, shouldn't we?
Tuh, ya.
See?
Tenang aja, gak bakal selama durasi stream Kaela kok, ya guys ya.
Don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's stream duration, guys.
Ya udahlah mau teriak-teriak, aku gak masalah, aku ikut.
Well, if you want to scream, I don't mind. I'll join.
Gimana nih semuanya? Udah siap belum?!
How is it, everyone? Are you ready yet?!
Siap!
Ready!
Siap nih kayaknya. Oke! Kobo dulu ya.
Looks like they're ready. Okay! Kobo first.
Aku mau kita sama-sama teriak...
I want us to scream together...
Baka, baka, baka!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Oke, siap ya?
Okay, ready?
Satu, dua, tiga!
One, two, three!
Baka, baka, baka!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Suka, suka, suka! Giliran Zeta, giliran Zeta.
Love it, love it, love it! Zeta's turn, Zeta's turn.
Aku, aku, oke, oke, oke.
Me, me, okay, okay, okay.
Pas aku bilang "Mission", kalian bareng-bareng teriak "Stato" ya.
When I say "Mission", you scream "Start" together, okay?
Siap?
Ready?
A-a-a... Mission...
Stato!
Start!
Yeay! Oke, habis ini Kaela.
Yay! Okay, next is Kaela.
Oke, oke, oke. Nah, ini ya buat semua penonton sama holoHero juga,
Okay, okay, okay. Now, this is for all the audience and also holoHero,
kalau misalnya aku bilang "Holo Hero", kalian bilang "Hoo-Haa!".
if I say "Holo Hero", you say "Hoo-Haa!".
Gampang kan? Langsung, langsung, langsung!
Easy, right? Right away, right away, right away!
Oke, oke, oke.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oke, ya. Siap ya? Holo Hero!
Okay. Ready? Holo Hero!
Hoo-Haa!
Mantap, mantap!
Awesome, awesome!
Mantap, mantap, mantap!
Awesome, awesome, awesome!
Keren, keren, keren. Akhirnya kita kompak juga.
Cool, cool, cool. Finally, we are in sync.
Iya, kompak.
Yes, in sync.
Kelihatannya masih pada semangat nih ya.
It seems everyone is still energetic.
Soalnya dari lagu pertama kita hari ini aja udah kerasa banget.
Because even from our first song today, we could really feel it.
Kalian tuh pada nyangka gak sih kalau lagu pertama kita tuh bakal 100%?
Did you guys expect our first song would be "100%"?
Buh, mana ada yang nyangka? Aku aja sendiri gak nyangka juga.
Pfft, who would have expected it? Even I myself didn't expect it.
Langsung dibuka dengan Hoshinova-mode gitu. Keren banget kan?
Starting right away with Hoshinova-mode like that. So cool, right?
Keren banget sih.
It was so cool.
Apalagi tadi Zeta sama nyanyi...
Especially when Zeta sang...
Zeta sama Kaela nyanyi 100% tuh udah kayak real 100% ya.
Zeta and Kaela singing "100%", it felt like a real 100%, right?
Itu tuh, bisa gak sih? Gak sekeren tadi aku tuh udah diiringin kayak...
Wait, can you? It wasn't as cool as when I was accompanied like...
Ugh, ugh! Gitu kan kalian pernah... kayak kalian pernah gak sih nyanyi lagu sekeren tadi?
Ugh, ugh! Like, have you guys ever sung a song as cool as that?
Aura farming ya?
Aura farming?
Aura farming, aura farming.
Bukan, lagunya keren banget emang lagunya Moona.
No, the song is really cool, it is Moona's song indeed.
Emang kan Zeta kan soalnya biasanya lagu-lagu yang jazzy, jazzy gitu.
Right, because Zeta usually sings stylish, jazzy songs.
Jadi tadi pas dinyanyiin tuh ya, 100%, rasanya jadi beda banget vibes-nya.
So when it was sung earlier, "100%", the vibe felt so different.
Terus Kaela juga tadi ngerap ya?
And Kaela was rapping too, right?
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta... Kayak apa tuh?
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta... Like what was that?
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Iya, pokoknya keren banget!
Yes, anyway, it was so cool!
Keren banget ya tadi.
It was so cool earlier.
Tapi habis ini tuh masih ada lagi, New Zombie.
But after this, there's still more, "New Zombie".
Ayo, pada tahu dong ini lagu siapa?
Come on, you guys know whose song this is, right?
Tahu lah, tahu lah. Senpai kita, senpai kita.
Of course we know, of course. Our senpai, our senpai.
Tadi tuh itu ya, Holoro tuh perform-nya juga keren banget kayak lagi di game gitu.
Earlier, Holoro's performance was also really cool, like being inside a game.
Betul, setuju.
True, I agree.
Terus tadi ada backdancer-nya men.
And there were backup dancers, man.
Keren ya, guys. Keren gak?
So cool, guys. Was it cool?
Tuh, ada apa lagi tuh tadi? Lampu laser, terus ada efek kembang api segala.
See, what else was there? Laser lights, and even firework effects.
Terus, banyaklah ya gimmick-gimmick yang wow.
And many other wow-inducing gimmicks.
Itu backdancer nanti aku sewa semua ya buat solo konser aku.
I'll hire all those backup dancers later for my solo concert.
Wah, udah ngomong konser solo aja.
Whoa, talking about a solo concert already.
Ini konser...
This concert...
Ya, omongan kan adalah doa, ya.
Well, words are prayers, right.
Iya.
Yes.
Tapi konser yang ini belum selesai.
But this concert isn't over yet.
Belum, belum, belum.
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Eh, tapi kalian tahu gak sih sebelum ini tuh nyanyinya lagu apa?
Eh, but do you guys know what song was sung before this?
Eh, aku mah tahu banget lah. Itu lagu terbaru aku.
Eh, I definitely know. That's my newest song.
Dala.
Ya? Udah?
Yeah? Already?
Nggak usah dibahas.
No need to discuss it.
Ya, udahlah.
Yeah, whatever.
Lho, kok gitu? Itu tuh maksudnya judulnya Dala! Lagunya judulnya Dala!
Wait, why like that? I mean the title is "Dala"! The song title is "Dala"!
Ohhh... iya, iya, iya. Oh, Dala.
Ohhh... yes, yes, yes. Oh, Dala.
Oh, Dala.
Bilang dong.
You should've said so.
Abisnya kamu kan sering "ya udahlah, ya udahlah" gitu, jadi dikirain emang beneran "ya udahlah".
Because you often say "whatever, whatever", so we thought you meant "whatever".
Ntar "Dala Dala" pulang dia.
Otherwise "Dala Dala" will go home.
Pulang nanti.
Go home later.
Kalau gitu, Dala tuh maksudnya apa sih?
If so, what does "Dala" mean anyway?
Dala, "sudahlah" sama kehidupan.
Dala, "let it be" with life.
Hidup tuh berat ya guys ya. Kalau hidup berat, ya udah, dala aja.
Life is hard, right guys. If life is hard, well, just "dala" (let it be).
Habis itu lanjutkan hidupmu. Begitu.
After that, continue your life. Like that.
Iya, betul teman-teman di kehidupan yang dewasa ini ya.
Yes, that's right friends, in this adult life, right.
Untuk lagu yang santai, easy listening...
Since it's a chill, easy-listening song...
...jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan ya, fans? Gitu ya?
...we can walk around while singing, right, fans? Isn't that right?
Asyik banget ya tadi, aku juga suka banget tadi dance bagian reff-nya ya.
It was so fun earlier! I also really liked the dance during the chorus.
Da la la da da la da la da da la da...
Itu... itu beda lagu enggak sih?
Wait... isn't that a different song?
Da la da da da...
Enggak gitu deh.
It's not like that.
Ya tapi pokoknya asyik lah ya...
But anyway, it's really fun...
...kalau nyanyi lagu chill, santai-santai kayak gini.
...to sing a chill, relaxing song like this.
Iya, santai dong.
Yeah, chill indeed.
Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu. Hei, santai!
But speaking of chilling, we actually can't chill just yet. Hey, chill!
Katanya enggak boleh santai, terus...
You said we can't chill, but then...
Iya, iya, jangan santai-santai.
Yeah, yeah, don't relax.
Jangan terlalu santai.
Don't be too relaxed.
Karena konsernya tuh masih panjang.
Because the concert is still far from over.
Jadi sebelum itu...
So before that...
...kalian ada enggak yang mau disampaikan dulu?
...is there anything you guys want to say first?
Mulai dari ini nih, yang enggak bisa diam.
Let's start with this one who can't stay still.
Tiga kata saja. I love you.
Just three words. I love you.
Keren, the best. Sangat jelas, ya.
Cool, the best. Very clear.
Tetap semangat. Tetap semangat menjalani hidup, ya.
Keep your spirits up. Keep your spirits up in living life.
Udah gitu aja, pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang.
That's all, anyway, it's still a long way till the end.
Semangat!
Keep fighting!
Saranghaeyo!
I love you!
Gomawoyo!
Thank you!
Oke kalau aku, ya, semangat selalu!
Okay, as for me, always keep your spirits up!
Semangat santai!
Keep your spirits up and stay chill!
Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya? Semangat santai.
Relaxed spirit, huh? Relaxed spirit.
Semangat santai!
Relaxed spirit!
Oke kalau gitu kita lanjut...
Okay then, let's continue...
Eits eits tunggu dulu. Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya...
Wait, wait, hold on. Before we finish all of this...
...kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu enggak sih?
...shouldn't we shout together with the audience first?
Iya dong! Ayo! Ayo!
Of course! Let's go! Let's go!
Oke, oke. Jadi kita teriak bareng ya?
Okay, okay. So we'll shout together, okay?
Dalam hitungan ketiga, kita sama-sama teriak Chromatic Future, oke ya?
On the count of three, we'll shout "Chromatic Future" together, alright?
Oke, oke, Chromatic Future, gitu kan ya?
Okay, okay, Chromatic Future, like that, right?
Iya, iya, kayak gitu, kayak gitu. Oke langsung ya.
Yes, yes, like that, like that. Okay, right away.
Sambil lihat, sini, sini, sini, sambil lihat.
While looking, here, here, here, while looking.
Aku ya, aku, aku yang penonton ini, penonton sini.
Me, me, I'll take this audience, the audience here.
Aku, aku ini deh, yang tengah, yang tengah. Halo...
I'll take this one, the middle, the middle. Hello...
Oke bareng-bareng ya. Satu, dua, tiga...
Okay, together. One, two, three...
Chromatic Future!
Everything was easy
I did it all alone
So effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic
unfold
Got all problems solved
Without any setbacks there is nothing uncontrolled
There is no way I can begin
To dream a life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher
Hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap
Like a peacock with its wings spread,
Kan kutaklukkan gelap dengan sihir angin
I will conquer the darkness with wind magic
Kan kuajak
I will invite
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
Everyone who is asleep to rise up
Melawan dunia
Against the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than that!
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Just believe me, let it go
It'll never bring me down, just believe me, let it go
It'll never bring us down, just believe me
Armed with their cruelties, still am of royalty
And when the universe works against me, I'll charge!
Let's go!
If it's spicy, just sip something, let it go
If it's spicy, just sip something, let it go!
Let's go!
I've been living carefree
There is no bitter woes in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
Not letting it show
Things might be bigger than my feelings so they'll be enough
There is no way I can begin to dream a life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
Semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia
All those who sleep, rise up to fight the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step
Trusting by your pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Just believe me, let it go
They'll never bring me down
They'll never bring us down, just believe me
Won't let their cruelty
Steal my royalty
And when the universe is once against me, I will just...
Let it go!
Come on guys, let's do this!
One, two, three, let it go!
hololive Indonesia CHROMATIC FUTURE 5th Anniversary LIVE